a responsible parent, it is your
responsibility to start your child's
future on the right foot so that
you can easily meet your child's future needs.
You should start planning your child's future plans today for your child
's future needs, such as education
and marriage.
Friends,
in this series, today we have brought the ICICI Prudential
Set Kar Fund. This is a dedicated channel
plan. Through this video, we will get
complete information about this plan
and also talk about
how you can invest in this fund.
Hello friends, welcome to the Punj Lloyd
YouTube channel. Friends, if you are visiting this channel for the
first time, then do not forget to subscribe to the channel.
This Set Kar Fund
is an offering of IDFC Mutual Fund, which is a Solution
Oriented Plan. Friends, this fund was
launched on 31 August 2002. This fund has
generated a very good return of 15.28% since its launch date. It is
based on the concept of mutual fund
whose benchmark index is Nifty Hybrid
Composite i.e.  In this, you get to
see the exposure of both equity and debt, in
which the daily share has been
kept at a maximum of 35 percent. If we talk about the next album, then
its value has currently reached
Rs 868 crore, which means that this much
money has been deposited by investors in this fund.
If you want to invest in this scheme, then
you will have to pay an expense ratio of 1.60 percent in Direct Bond.
Friends, expense ratio is the
cost of investing in mutual funds. Presently,
this mutual fund scheme is being
managed by Ashwin Jain, Manish Jain and Ritesh Lunawat.
Friends, fund managers are those
who manage the portfolio of the mutual fund, that is, the
fund manager decides where
your money will be invested. The
portfolio of this scheme
is made up of both equity and debt,
whose effective portion currently has 22
stocks. If we talk about the latest of this scheme, then the
average return of the last 5 years
is 98 percent, whereas the
average of the last three years is 11.68 percent.  In the last one
year, this scheme has given a return of 11.13%.
If you had invested
Rs 1 lakh in this channel's fund on January 1, 2013, then at the
present
time i.e. in February 2012, the
value of your investment would have increased to 3.13%. Consequently,
your annual return would have been
31.24%. If you had started a
SIP of Rs 10,000 per month instead of lump sum on January 1, 2013, then as on
today's date, your
total investment would have been Rs 5 lakh 50
thousand, whose maturity value would have been
10.06%. In such an investment made in UP Board,
your average monthly
return would have come out to be 12.73%.
Investment planning friends, if you start
Manch Pradhan Mantri Investment in this scheme with Rs 5000
and
continue it till this year, then your
total investment in this would have been Rs 1 lakh.
If we take the average annual return at the rate of 12%  If we
add, then after the base year,
our maturity will be ₹5000000. This means that
if you start this investment when your child is two-three years old, then by the
age of this year, you will have
accumulated ₹50 lakh. If you
invest ₹2 lakh in this scheme instead of lump sum investment, then
after this year, at the rate of 12% return,
your maturity will be ₹21.80 lakh.
If you wish, you
can also top up your lump sum investment from time to time, this will
increase the value you get on the table. Now let's talk about who can
invest in this scheme. Any
individual or children or their
parents
can open an account for them. If you want to invest in this scheme, then you
can start this scheme on SEBI basis, whereas
you can start a lump sum with a minimum of ₹5000. The
money deposited in this scheme remains locked for 5 years,
i.e.  You cannot withdraw that money for 5 years,
but the condition for this
is that when your deposited money attains maturity for 5 years or
when your child attains
18 years of age, that is,
you can withdraw your money in whichever of these two conditions is fulfilled first.
Suppose you
invested in this scheme today for your 15-year-old child. Now
your child will attain the age of 18 years after three years.
In this condition, you
can withdraw the money from this scheme without
any exit load. Similarly, if your
child is only 5 years old, then you will have to
invest a minimum of five items in this scheme.
How to invest: Now I have told you that you can
invest in three ways:
first through a broker,
second through the official website of ICSE Mutual Fund,
third through a mobile app.
I would suggest you to
start your investment through the mobile app of stocks. In this
mobile, now you get the
facility of all mutual funds, stocks, IPOs.
In stocks, you can go to the
link given in the description.  You can open your demat account
Friends, if you
invest in the funds of this channel, then you
get exposure to both equity plus debit,
this reduces the amount of your face to a great extent
If you invest in this scheme for a long time, then
you can
get good maturity value
Also, due to the 5 year login,
your investment dip will remain long
But if you like to take high risk, then
you can start your investment with pure equity fund,
but in pure equity fund you may have to face high risk,
along with this you have the
possibility of getting good returns
Friends, I hope that
you liked the information given in this video
Friends, please show your support by liking the video
and definitely share this video with someone in need So
friends, let's meet again with some new information.